Sometimes it feels like life is in a big loop because we just go around the same little circles, the
same cycles.
Wake up.
Do the x, y, z things.
Come home, have some dinner, go to bed.
Wake up.
It's loops, loops, loops.
The loops are an important part of life because that's how things work.
And they're also an important part when it comes to our coding.
Now, I might not be Froot Loops, but coding has an important aspect, and that is the use of loops,
because we looked earlier at how to make decisions.
But sometimes we need things to repeat multiple times.
So we might want to say let's go around a loop until a certain condition is true.
Or let's go around a loop three times doing something.
So in this section we want to have a look at loops and how they are very powerful and useful in coding.
So get the thinking cap on.
Get ready as we have a look at the power of loops in Python.